Finding Aid for the S. Charles Lee papers LSC.1384
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Plans/Renderings
  - Visalia Theatre (Golden State Theatres), Visalia (Folder 247)
  - Vogue Theatre (Fox West Coast & South Gate Theatres), South Gate (Folder 264)
  - Vogue Theatre (Sheehan & Sinks), Hollywood (Folder 264)
  - Wasco Theatre (Frank Panero), Wasco (Folder 264)
  - Weinberg (Milton) - Advertising Agency Office (Folder 306)
  - Weisman (Sidney M.) - Café, Los Angeles (Folder 306)
  - Weisman (Sidney M.) - Super Bowl Service Station, Los Angeles (Folder 190)
  - Weisman (Sidney M.) - Super Bowl Service Station, Los Angeles (Folder 306)
  - Weisman (Sidney M.) - Super Bowl Service Station, Los Angeles (Folder 306)
  - Westlake Theatre (Fox West Coast), Los Angeles (Folder 264)
  - Whitelock (Frank L.) housing, San Bernadino (Folder 187)
    (see Bunker Hill Square)`
  - Wickman (Emil) - residence, Whittier Heights (Folder 187)
  - Wolfson Brothers Co. Building, Los Angeles (Folder 307)
  - Woodbury College, Los Angeles (Folder 206)
  - Woodruff (W.M.) - (Thrifty Drug Store), Hollywood (Folder 307)
  - Wright's Men Store, Whittier (Folder 307)
  - Wurlitzer (Howard) Theatre / Office, Cincinnati (Folder 256)
  - Wurlitzer Office/Theatre, Cincinatti (Folder 141)
  - Yanow Theatre, Hollywood (Folder 256)
  - Zukor (J.H.) - residence, Los Angeles (Folder 187)